in best videos lifestyle by several most personal details
最佳影片生活方式中最重要的几个个人资料
one of the strypes is the we do everything priced how many views my video
其中的一大障碍是我们会尽一切努力定价我的视频的观看次数
about Bloemers god and after reading comments and realize that many young
关于布洛默斯（Bloemers）神，并在阅读评论后意识到很多年轻
people identified him even numbers 5 mixed
人们发现他甚至是5个混合的数字
feelings about this picas after all the denominator is the trajectory
毕竟分母是轨迹，对这种异食癖的感受
product of the modern world that is not only gay de bypass experiences and also
现代世界的产物，不仅是同性恋的绕行经历，而且
in the spare of you manage your future beringen stoicism enthusiastic he will
在您的忙碌中，您将热情地管理您的未来beringen狂热主义者
to myself incubator is a bs illusion or at
对我自己而言，孵化器是一种错觉或幻想
least a am dutch for the doers software in this video outlight percent
在此视频中，doers软件至少是荷兰人
je or you stole my ideas to the hurt the doers
je还是你偷了我的想法给行动者带来了伤害
like many people the song is a camber which is a song of things that
像许多人一样，这首歌是外倾曲，是一首歌，
aren't really up to him a cm thick as the doer mimi arno happens to be e-mail en
真的不像他那么厚，因为doer mimi arno恰好是电子邮件
the team put majority of tumor or mails eventhough the problem is a narrow one
研究小组将大部分肿瘤或邮件都放了进去，尽管问题是一个狭窄的问题
female minority occasionally arise lest i was the mail version for simplistic
少数女性偶尔会出现，以免我被简化了
the pushers depression and spro big eyes further training the profile reptile
推杆凹陷和spro大眼睛进一步训练剖面爬行动物
the belt need too much whether i agree and i s'pose into many resin realities or
皮带是否需要太多，无论我是否同意，我是否会摆在很多树脂现实中或
the world be cause i realize the reality as much
世界是因为我也意识到现实
younger than the previously error yes fallen into a pc and last the ability
比以前的错误还年轻，属于个人电脑，并具有持续的能力
to find and joy in a world there is already oil gas style and evil in one
在一个世界中找到快乐，已经有石油和邪恶的气息了
age of moral declined what's there to push site smoking weed some shampoo
道德时代下降了什么来推动现场吸烟除草一些洗发水
drinking beer and playing video games mainly do for you
喝啤酒和玩电子游戏主要为您效劳
many years ago he wins floor several existential crisis
许多年前，他赢得了几次生存危机
jerry detail and death in my search for trump find out more about human
杰里·细节和死亡在我寻找特朗普的过程中找到了更多有关人类的信息
nature and the dark side of boys society may
大自然和男孩社会的阴暗面
be absolutely miserable and that he whistles and substances and porn do anything but
绝对是悲惨的，他吹口哨，吹嘘物质和色情除了
long before the doom there was a fang fc oh what have i got to realize in macho
在厄运发生之前很久，有一个恶作剧哦。
bold sometimes beyond my control one of
有时大胆超出我的控制范围之一
the great stowbox takes epictetus realize this many centuries ago i conclu
巨大的储物盒需要Epictetus意识到，这是几个世纪前我总结的
the that we should not waist or time focusing on tanks that there is a tattoo
我们不应该腰部或时间集中在有纹身的坦克上
who should focus on the things that are up to was in style the dimmer may be
谁应该专注于调光器可能符合的事物
completely just in the world view and be very well in
完全在世界范围内，并且在
beyond declining western civilization and even the possibility of a third
超越了正在下降的西方文明，甚至还有三分之一的可能性
world war also i may look down upon the norm
我也可能看不起世界大战
by economic boat and towards keynote
乘经济船向主题演讲
nonetheless epictetus it must be that door mix and great mistake
尽管如此，那肯定是门混和很大的错误
that course is mary keith completly wasting time feeling measurable about
那门课程是玛丽·基思（Marie keith）完全浪费时间而感到无法衡量的
things that are not up to hem d66 side-effect which is the indulgence in
不属于下摆d66副作用的东西
sanyo pleasures then took the pain and fly from reality
然后，三洋享乐从现实中解脱出来
according to the store x in temperance is a vice and so is cowers
根据商店的说法，节制是恶习，退缩也是
opinions of other people politics of genetics
遗传学的其他人的观点
these things arbi other control but there's news
这些东西都是其他控制权，但有新闻
there something weird your control which is a room faculty
房间里有一些奇怪的东西由您控制
the truth is that it is not the events that comes mary that the pictures about
事实是，图片所涉及的不是事件本身
those events' choir and toe epictetus who couldn't get
那些事件的合唱团和脚趾上的遗言
hang an outside events what come except and so
挂个外界事件，除了什么
that's that mean that we should be indifferent to watch you and suffering
那意味着我们应该冷漠地看着你和痛苦
and in justice tuin nou not at all one of the storevirtual is justice this means
在正义中，根本没有一家商店是真正的正义，这意味着
that we should make an effort to treat other people well and over time
我们应该努力并随着时间的推移善待他人
value to the community how to separate unfortunately
对社区的价值不幸的是如何分开
had to do there sun living in isolation a star or seeking the connection
必须在那里做太阳，让它孤立地生活在恒星中或寻找联系
they were two smoking drinking and drive safely and off the sphinx make them more
他们是两个抽烟喝酒并安全驾驶的人，而狮身人面像则使他们更加
dretful in the longer or fluffy punch is highly
在较长或蓬松的拳头中沉闷是高度
curt words one's own mind that puts great emphasis on meaning for connection
轻描淡写强调联系意义的自己的思想
with other young babies two praises control how the external world race
与其他幼儿一起，两个赞美控制了外部世界的竞赛
effected by your actions helping others and connecting with lemon
受您帮助他人并与柠檬联系在一起的行为的影响
and meaningful we will most likely have a positive effect wet underworld
有意义的是，我们很可能会对地下世界产生积极影响
and it is a week or even luckily there
那是一个星期，甚至幸运的是
ways to reconnect with young bx work sport hobbies
与年轻的bx工作爱好重新建立联系的方式
community work volunteering jona with so lord rail
社区工作志愿乔纳与如此的主铁路
dessing epictetus would say to dimmers city mumbai yourself and face reality
欲罢不能的话将对孟买调光器市自己说并面对现实
hair care less about things that aren't up to you and find purpose for
少去照顾那些不适合您的事情，并找到适合自己的目标
connection with other people also at word to realize everyone's effect
与其他人的交流也可以实现每个人的作用
was not only your slave who was crippled tess though
不仅是你的奴隶残废了苔丝
not to mention that i live in a file and time in a file and civilization iv
更不用说我生活在一个档案中，时间生活在一个档案与文明中iv
can find happiness and pressure to do that work and to thank you for watching
可以找到幸福和压力去做这项工作，并感谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]